To access your Microsoft Office
programs, you would need to go
down to the start menu, which is
in the bottom left hand corner.
If you click on the Windows icon,
that will bring up a list of programs
that are installed on your computer.
Everything is installed alphabetically,
so as you scroll down, you will see
the programs that have been installed
such as Excel, PowerPoint and Word,
which are the three programs that
you will use during this course.
To access the program, you would
simply click on the Word icon, and then
that would open up, Microsoft Word.
To make it easier to access
your software without having
to go through the start menu.
You can right click on that.
And then select the more
option and pin to task bar.
This will then place the
icon on your task bar.
So by clicking on that, that will
open the program directly without
having to go through the start menu.
You can then do this for your
PowerPoint and your Excel, which will
just speed things up a little bit.
If I click on the icon now that
will launch Word and take me to
the Good Morning welcome screen.